arcadebomb.com 2017-11-28

# Privacy Policy for ArcadeBomb.com

|  |  Privacy Policy : Statement  
---  
  
## Statement

This statement is the official published ("Privacy Policy") for arcadebomb.com ("Site," "we," "us," or "our"), a gaming portal owned and operated by Explosive Games Networks, Inc. This Privacy Policy governs only the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") collected by the Site. FPS is committed to protecting your privacy online. To further this commitment, we have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information collected about you online. 

## Full privacy!

Your privacy is 100% guaranteed at arcadebomb.com. Arcadebomb is committed to protecting your privacy online. Arcadebomb.com does not collect or store any personal information on its servers. At arcadebomb.com your gaming experience is a truely safe experience as well !! Dear end user (game player); Keep in mind that Arcadebomb does allow third parties to advertise on its website. Keep reading this page to learn more about our third parties. 

## What are cookies?

Cookies are digital text files that can be created by any remote connection that you make in your browser. A cookie can only store text or (binairy) numbers or a combinations of both. Because cookies are just text files, created and controlled by your browser, it's a harmless system for your computer health. However you need to be aware that websites, mobile apps and advertisers are able to write and read certain 'invisible' information on the background while you think you are just browsing some online or mobile App content.

Our webserver html, php and scripts do not execute any code that create tracking cookies. Our webserver is configured to create no log files other then emergency crash dumps. However please be aware that we are using third-party scripts (for example, but not limited to, advertisements) that might use cookies - please read the third party section of our privacy policy for more information about our third parties. 

## IP tracking

Arcadebomb keeps NO logs of IP address or any other information used to track broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc) Arcadebomb does not store personal, or individual data on its servers, we respect your privacy and strongly believe that maintaining privacy, as an independant portal, is one of our main objectectives. Arcadebomb keeps no logs of any clicks or visits; we only focus on being an awesome free gaming website with daily updates and the best exclusive flash games! 

## Sharing Of Information

There are no scripts or programs running on our server that store your information. We allow our third party advertisers to host scripts on our webpages. Third party advertisers might collect, store and use your information. These scripts are not property of our game portal website and are subject to the privacy policy of the third party. Find the links to the third party privacy policies in the sections below to learn more. 

## Third Parties

We use third-party scripts, such as, but not limited to, advertising (OBA) companies to serve (content) ads when you visit arcadebomb.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Third party policy links:

\- Google Adsense - [www.google.com/adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense)  
\- Google Cookies Policy - [google.com/privacy_cookies.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html)  
\- Adsense Privacy policy - [google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
\- Cpmstar - [www.cpmstar.com](http://www.cpmstar.com/)

Used third party scripts are served by Google and Cpmstar.

## Cookie Policy

\- In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

\- Visit nai opt out to protect your privacy. Note that by using the nai opt out service you will create cookies on your machine, created by nai itself.

## Opt Out Cookies

It is possible to protect yourself from unwanted cookies by using the opt out service. Please note that the opt out service is creating cookies itself too!  

## No Server Logs

Our server software has disabled log files to speed up your game experience. Allowing the visitor to have a good and fast game experience. The current log level of the server is set to EMERG. Meaning that the server will only make a small (text) log dump in the event of a server crash. This allows us to harden and improve your gaming experience in the rare occurrence of a server problem.  

## Liability & Copyright

It is arcadebomb.com's policy to respond quickly (under 24 hours) to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, arcadebomb.com will immediately disable and remove games in question. Please take some time to read our copyright policy read more

_this policy was published on 2010 by Explosive Games_  
Arcadebomb.com 

|  |  Game Banner

The best free online flash games are rotated in this box, stay up to date with the latest in free games!

|   
---|---  
|  Flash Games

Try this flash game if you are looking for more then our 1000 web arcade games on our internet gaming site.

|   
---|---
